http://www.espseeds.com/privacy-policy

Login | Register
My Basket
0 items
checkout
Seed CatalogFeatured ProductsSeed By RegionWildflower Seed and MixturesGarden and Herb SeedSeed SearchOrdering InformationRequirementsShippingReturnsResourcesWildflower Planting GuidePlanting RatesCatalogHelpContact UsFAQAboutNews
Find Seeds:
Organic SeedOrganic Vegetable SeedOrganic Flower SeedOrganic Herb SeedFeatured ProductsFeatured Seed and MixturesTop SellersBee Friendly Seed by RegionIntermountain SeedMidwest SeedNorthwestern SeedNortheast SeedSoutheast SeedSouthwest SeedTexas and Oklahoma SeedWest Coast SeedWillamette Valley - NativesWildflower Seed and MixturesRegional Wildflower MixturesNative Wildflower MixturesNative Wildflower SeedSpecial Purpose MixturesGarden Flower Garden Flower and Naturalizing SeedHerb Seed
Privacy Policy
Home >
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To Your Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy
the following notice explains the information we collect, how it is
used, how it is safeguarded, and how to contact us if you have any
concerns.
Collection and Use of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names,
postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted
by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill
your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill
your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in
another manner.
The Security of Your Data
We may share information with governmental agencies or other
companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may
do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to
protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or
unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has
already taken place.
The information is not provided to these companies for marketing
purposes.
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only
authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to
keep information secure and confidential) have access to this
information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to
opt out of further mailings.
Contact Us
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our
privacy policy you may contact us using the information
below.  Our offices are open from 7:30 am - 4:30 pm Pacific
Standard Time, Monday thru Friday.
ESP Seeds
P.O. Box 947
Albany, OR 97321-0354
USA
805-733-4975
541-928-5868
Fax: 541-928-5581
Email: cindy@wildflowerseed.com
Seed by RegionIntermountain RegionMidwest RegionNorthwest RegionSoutheast RegionSouthwest RegionTexas and Oklahoma SeedWest Coast SeedWildflower Seed and MixturesRegional Wildflower Seed MixturesNative Wildflower MixesNative Wildflower SeedSpecial Purpose Seed MixturesGarden Flower SeedGarden Flower and Naturalizing SeedFeatured ProductsFeatured Seed and MixturesTop SellersBee FriendlyOrdering InformationRequirementsShippingReturnsResourcesAbout Organic SeedWildflower Planting GuidePlanting RatesAboutNewsHelp (FAQ)ContactWebsiteWholesale Seed SearchCreate a New AccountYour AccountSecure ShoppingPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseSitemapAll Seed Products
Copyright ©
Environmental Seed Producers
